{
  "questions": [
    {
      "qid": "p1u2-f1",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "_____________ are you, Ella?",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "How old",
      "fullSentence": "How old are you, Ella?",
      "questionHint": "Speak the complete sentences with 'How old' or 'years old'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u2-f2",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "I am seven ______________.",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "years old",
      "fullSentence": "I am seven years old.",
      "questionHint": "Speak the complete sentences with 'How old' or 'years old'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u2-f3",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "_____________ is your sister, Rose?",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "How old",
      "fullSentence": "How old is your sister, Rose?",
      "questionHint": "Speak the complete sentences with 'How old' or 'years old'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u2-f4",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "She is ten ______________.",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "years old",
      "fullSentence": "She is ten years old.",
      "questionHint": "Speak the complete sentences with 'How old' or 'years old'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u2-f5",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "_____________ are you, Jack and Mark?",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "How old",
      "fullSentence": "How old are you, Jack and Mark?",
      "questionHint": "Speak the complete sentences with 'How old' or 'years old'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u2-f6",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "We are five ______________.",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "years old",
      "fullSentence": "We are five years old.",
      "questionHint": "Speak the complete sentences with 'How old' or 'years old'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u2-f7",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "_____________ is your cat?",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "How old",
      "fullSentence": "How old is your cat?",
      "questionHint": "Speak the complete sentences with 'How old' or 'years old'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u2-f8",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "It is three ______________.",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "years old",
      "fullSentence": "It is three years old.",
      "questionHint": "Speak the complete sentences with 'How old' or 'years old'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u2-f9",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "_____________ are you, Jay?",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "How old",
      "fullSentence": "How old are you, Jay?",
      "questionHint": "Speak the complete sentences with 'How old' or 'years old'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1u2-f10",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "I am six _____________________.",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "years old",
      "fullSentence": "I am six years old.",
      "questionHint": "Speak the complete sentences with 'How old' or 'years old'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1Bu2-g1",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "I _____ many toys.",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "have",
      "fullSentence": "I have many toys.",
      "questionHint": "Fill in the blanks with 'have' or 'has'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1Bu2-g2",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "She ____ a new doll.",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "has",
      "fullSentence": "She has a new doll.",
      "questionHint": "Fill in the blanks with 'have' or 'has'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1Bu2-g3",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "It _____ three balls.",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "has",
      "fullSentence": "It has three balls.",
      "questionHint": "Fill in the blanks with 'have' or 'has'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1Bu2-g4",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "Mike and Sam ____ ten robots.",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "have",
      "fullSentence": "Mike and Sam have ten robots.",
      "questionHint": "Fill in the blanks with 'have' or 'has'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1Bu2-g5",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "He _____ a balloon.",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "has",
      "fullSentence": "He has a balloon.",
      "questionHint": "Fill in the blanks with 'have' or 'has'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1Bu2-g6",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "We _____ no puzzles.",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "have",
      "fullSentence": "We have no puzzles.",
      "questionHint": "Fill in the blanks with 'have' or 'has'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1Bu2-g7",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "Lily _____ two teddy bears.",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "has",
      "fullSentence": "Lily has two teddy bears.",
      "questionHint": "Fill in the blanks with 'have' or 'has'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1Bu2-g8",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "You _____ some toy planes.",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "have",
      "fullSentence": "You have some toy planes.",
      "questionHint": "Fill in the blanks with 'have' or 'has'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1Bu2-g9",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "They _____ blue, red and yellow toy trucks.",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "have",
      "fullSentence": "They have blue, red and yellow toy trucks.",
      "questionHint": "Fill in the blanks with 'have' or 'has'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p1Bu2-g10",
      "questionType": "FillInBlank",
      "question": "Ken _____ twenty toy cars.",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "has",
      "fullSentence": "Ken has twenty toy cars.",
      "questionHint": "Fill in the blanks with 'have' or 'has'."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a1",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "blow soap bubbles",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a2",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "chase butterflies",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a3",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "eat marshmallows",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a4",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "fly a kite",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a5",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "light a fire",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a6",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "play hide-and-seek",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a7",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "ride a bicycle",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a8",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "go hiking",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a9",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "have barbecues",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a10",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "climb a tree",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a11",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "see a rainbow",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a12",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "ride a horse",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a13",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "tell a ghost story",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a14",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "play a card game",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a15",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "go fishing",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a16",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "set up a tent",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a17",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "sail on a yacht",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a18",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "try outdoor cooking",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a19",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "sunbathe",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    },
    {
      "qid": "p3Bu4-a20",
      "questionType": "Audio",
      "question": "",
      "answers": null,
      "correctAnswer": "row a boat",
      "questionHint": "Listen and speak the phrases."
    }
  ]

}